vyew.com 2006-10-22

# Vyew.com - Free Web-Based Collaboration - Vyew.com - Free Web-Based Collaboration

[Home](http://www1.vyew.com/?n=Main.Home) » Privacy Policy 

Related pages: [Terms of Service](http://www1.vyew.com/?n=Main.VyewServiceAgreement)

#### Your privacy is important, so we have created the following Privacy and Security Policy to let you know what information we collect when you transact with Simulat, as well as why we collect it, and how it is used. 

This Privacy and Security Policy also addresses our data security practices, the options you have to access and control any personally identifiable information you provide to us, and other matters. This Privacy and Security Policy is governed by our Terms and Conditions. We may periodically make changes to this Privacy and Security Policy which will be included on this page. It is your responsibility to review this Privacy and Security Policy frequently and remain informed about any changes to it, so we encourage you to visit this page often.

### Special note about children

This Site is not intended for or directed to persons under the age of 18. By registering with this web site or providing Simulat with any information, you represent that you are 18 years of age or older and that any information you provide to Simulat about a third party is for a third party that is 18 years of age or older.  

### What information do we collect from you? Why?

We may collect information needed to contact you later. If we collect personal contact information (as described below), you may later access and modify it, and remove it from our system. You may also choose simply not to provide your personal contact information at the point of collection.  

### We may collect your name, address and phone number

When you use Vyew, we may request your first and last name, home or other physical address, including your street name and address and name of your city or town, your telephone number or other "real world" contact information.  
We use this information to complete the transaction, for internal purposes and to comply with any requirements of law. This information may be disclosed to our staff and to third parties involved in the completion of your transaction, the delivery of your order or the analysis and support of your use of Vyew.  

### We may collect your email address

We may request your email address, or other information needed to contact you online. We use it to complete, support and analyze the transaction. We use it to respond to any questions you might have and perhaps to provide you with information about future use of our product. This information may be disclosed to our staff and to third parties involved in the completion of your transaction, the delivery of your order or the analysis and support of your use of Vyew.  

### We may collect other kinds of information from you

When you use our web site, we may collect personal information about you described below. You may later access and modify the information, or have it removed. You may also simply choose not to provide your personal contact information at the point of collection; however, if you do not provide such information, we may be unable to complete your transaction.  

### We may collect purchase information

We may collect information actively generated by the purchase of our service, such as a payment method. We use this information to process your order and analyze and support your use of Vyew. This information may be disclosed only to our staff and to third parties involved in the completion of your transaction or the analysis and support of your transaction.  

### We may collect navigation and clickstream data

As you browse our web site, we may gather navigational and clickstream data that shows what pages are visited and how long various features are used. This information will not reveal your identity or be linked to you personally. We use this information to complete, analyze and support your transaction with Vyew and to comply with any requirements of law and to determine the commissions for our affiliate partners. This information may be disclosed only to our staff and to third parties involved in the completion of your transaction, the delivery of your order, and the analysis and support of your use of Vyew.  

### We may use third-party affiliate partners to deliver customers to our site

These companies may employ cookies and action tags (also known as single pixel gifs or web beacons) to measure advertising effectiveness. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and action tags is completely anonymous.  

### Certain exception disclosures

We may disclose your information if necessary to protect our legal rights, if the information relates to actual or threatened harmful conduct, or Vyew has good faith belief that such action is necessary to (1) conform to the requirements of law or comply with governmental orders, court orders, or legal process served on Vyew or its parent company or (2) to protect and defend the property or rights of Vyew, the users of its website or the public. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk protection. If Vyew or its parent company should ever file for bankruptcy or merge with another company, we may sell the information you provide to us on the Vyew website to a third party or share your personal information with the company we merge with.  

### What are cookies? Why do we use them?

Cookies are very tiny text files that are stored on your computer when you visit certain web pages that record your preferences. Vyew may use cookies to recognize you when you return to Vyew. They cannot harm your computer and they do not contain any personal or private information.  

### How do we protect information we collect?

We offer secure web pages to collect certain kinds of user information and we store certain kinds of data in encrypted form. We follow reasonable technical and management practices to help protect the confidentiality, security and integrity of data stored on our system. While no computer system is completely secure, we believe the measures implemented by our web site reduce the likelihood of security problems to a level appropriate to the type of data involved. Vyew’s servers use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL), an encryption technology that works with Netscape Navigator, Microsoft Internet Explorer, and AOL's browser, so that only Vyew can read a customer's personal information.  

### How long do we keep user information?

We generally keep user data on our server or in our archives for as long as we reasonably need it. We may alter this practice according to changing requirements. For example, we may delete some data if needed to free up storage space. We may keep other data for longer periods if the law requires it. In addition, information posted in a public forum could stay in the public domain indefinitely.   
Data management requests are administered in an orderly manner to the extent feasible and within our direct control. Note: we have greater control over recently collected data than for archived data. Once data is removed from the system and archived, it may not be feasible to accommodate specific requests. In those cases, our general data retention policy applies.  

### Third party sites

This Site contains links to third party websites, including sites of hotel providers that serve as affiliate partners of Simulat. Simulat is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. Your use of these third party websites is entirely at your own risk. When you click on a link in an Offer Detail, you are essentially taken to the originating affiliate partner’s site.  

### Your consent to this policy

By using the Vyew service, you agree to this Privacy and Security Policy. This is our entire and exclusive Privacy and Security Policy and it supersedes any earlier version. Our Terms and Conditions take precedence over any conflicting Policy provision. We may change our Privacy and Security Policy by posting a new version of the policy on this page which it is your responsibility to review frequently.  

### Legal disclaimer

This Site operates AS-IS and AS-AVAILABLE, without liability of any kind. We are not responsible for events beyond our direct control. This Privacy and Security Policy is governed by California law, excluding conflicts of law principles. Any legal actions against us must be commenced in California within one year after the claim arose, or be barred.
